<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Learn Anything</string>
    <string name="menu_definctions_text_pl">Theoretical issues</string>
    <string name="menu_tasks_text_pl">Tasks</string>


    <string-array name="subjects_array">
        <item>Physics</item>
        <item>Electronic</item>
        <item>Math</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--electronic-->
    <string-array name="electronic_defs_name">
        <item>Ohm law</item>
        <item>I Kirchhoff Law</item>
        <item>II Kirchhoff Law</item>
        <item>Thevenin theorem</item>
        <item>An ideal and real power source</item>
    </string-array>
    <!--electronic defs-->
    <string-array name="electronic_defs">
        <!--ohm-->
        <item>
            This law associates current and voltage with a resistor resistance.\n
            I=U/R I[A]=U[V]/R[Ω] R[Ω]=U[V]/I[A]\n
            I - current flowing through the resistor expressed in Amps A\n
            U - voltage applied to the resistor expressed in volts V\n
            R - resistor resistance expressed in Ohms Ω\n
        </item>
        <!--        IKirchoff-->
        <item>
            The sum of the currents flowing into the network node equals the sum of the currents flowing from the network node.
        </item>
        <!--        IIKirchoff-->
        <item>
            The sum of the source voltages in the grid mesh equals the sum of the decreases in the receiver voltages in the grid mesh.
        </item>
        <!--        TwThev.-->
        <item>
            Any system can be replaced from the side of the AB terminals with a system composed of an ideal source
            voltage, with the voltage prevailing on the AB terminals in idle state (without load)
            and from the equivalent resistance seen from the AB terminals (in idle state) after a short circuit
            all voltage sources and all current sources open.
        </item>
        <!--idealne i rzeczy.-->
        <item>

        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="electronic_defs_pics">
        <item>ohm</item>
        <item>ikichoff</item>
        <item>iikirchoff</item>
        <item>thevenin</item>
        <item>iirzp</item>
    </string-array>


    <!--    physics-->
    <string-array name="physics_defs_name">
        <item>Newton first law of dynamics</item>
        <item>Newton second law of dynamics</item>
        <item>Newton third law of dynamics</item>
        <item>Analytical and graphic presentation of the equation of motion as well as the time dependence of velocity and acceleration in uniformly accelerated one-dimensional motion</item>
        <item>Analytical and graphical presentation of the equation of motion and time dependence of velocity and acceleration in uniform one-dimensional motion</item>
        <item>Movement of the body projected at an angle to the horizon: analytical and graphic description</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="physics_defs">
        <!--INewton-->
        <item>
            If the body is not affected by external forces,
            or acting forces balance,
            this body remains at rest or moves in a uniform, straight motion.
            F=m*g, where\n
            F- force [N]\n
            m- body weight [kg]\n
            g- gravitational acceleration [N/kg]\n
            Application e.g. ball lying on the table
        </item>
        <!--        IINewton-->
        <item>
            The acceleration of the body is directly proportional to the force acting on it and inversely proportional to its mass.\n
            This law can be expressed by the equation: force is equal to mass multiplied by acceleration (F = ma).
        </item>
        <!--        IIINetwon-->
        <item>
            Each action evokes an equal and opposite reaction.\
            Newton law of universal gravitation states that there is an attractive, proportional force between the two bodies\
            to their masses and inversely proportional to the square of the distance between them.
        </item>
<!--        ruch jednostanie przyszp.-->
        <item>
            Motion - changing the position of one body relative to another, which we call the reference system.\n
            Speed ​​- change of distance in a unit of time.\n
            Acceleration - is the rate of change of speed uniform acceleration a = v-v0/t
        </item>

        <item>
            Motion - changing the position of one body relative to another, which we call the reference system. \n
            Speed ​​- change of distance in a unit of time. \ n
            Acceleration - is the rate of speed change \ n
            Speed ​​in steady motion - v = x-x<sub>0</sub>/t-t<sub>0</sub>
        </item>

        <item>

        </item>


    </string-array>


    <string-array name="physics_defs_pics">
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="on_choose_learn_kind_text">choose_value</string>
    <string name="on_choose_learn_subject_text">subject_value</string>
    <string name="on_choose_def_text">def_value</string>
    <string name="def_body_text">def_body</string>
    <string name="def_img_text">def_img</string>
    <string name="images_folder_name_text">drawable</string>

</resources>
